[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '結婚します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けっこんします"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '登録します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とうろくします"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '登録' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とうろく"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '釣りします' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "つりします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '会議します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいぎします"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '会議' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいぎ"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '食事します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくじします"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '食事' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょくじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '買い物します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいものします"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '買い物' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいもの"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お腹が空きました' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おなかがすきました"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お腹がいっぱい' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おなかがいっぱい"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '咽が乾きました' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のどがかわきました"
    }
]
